Grove Press Records
Grove Press Records
- Books - Book files (by author)
  - Roy, Claude
    - Zao Wou-Ki
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1958-1960; includes color photographs and clippings of color plates, photograph of author (Box 611)
      - Production, Setting copy, text only; typescript with corrections (Box 611)
      - Publicity, 1960-1961 (Box 611)
  - Roy, Jules
    - The War in Algeria
      - Correspondence, 1960-1961; includes background material "Algeria: Questions and Answers," Feb 1961 issue of The Arab World, October 1960 statement from The Algerian Office in New York on the war (Box 611)
      - Photographs, Author (Box 611)
      - Production, Typescript and galleys (partial), typescript drafts of two chapters; typescript and galleys of introduction by David Schoenbrun (Box 611)
      - Publicity, 1960; long article in French from L'Express; Grove blurb (Box 611)
      - Royalties, Borchardt / Juillard (T-2), 1961-1965 (Box 611)
  - Rozewicz, Tadeusz
    - The Card Index and Other Plays
      - Contract, Calder and Boyars, 1966 (Box 611)
      - Contract, Lyons and Harte, 1967 (Box 611)
      - Contract, Samuel French, 1971 (Box 611)
      - Correspondence, 1699-1971; most is with Calder & Boyars (Box 611)
      - Production, Jacket, includes typescript drafts of jacket copy (Box 611)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1969 (Box 611)
      - Production, Photographs, from Teatru Dramatycznego performance (Box 611)
      - Production, Setting copy, marked-up Calder and Boyars edition (Box 611)
      - Publicity, 1970-1971 (Box 611)
      - Royalties, Calder and Boyars (E-538), 1967-1970 (Box 611)
  - Rozov, Viktor
    - In Search of Happiness / Uneven Combat
      - Contract, 1962 (Box 611)
      - Correspondence, 1962-1963; 1967; includes clipping of one article by Rozov and typescript of another, both from Soviet Weekly (Box 611)
      - Royalties, Am-Rus Literary Agency, 1962; 1966-1971 (Box 611)
  - Rubington, Norman
    - Cliches
      - Correspondence, Author, 1960; 1964; includes letter from his wife Yvonne about "Le clochard" (Box 611)
  - Rudkin, David
    - Afore Night Come
      - Contract, copyright form, 1963; 1991 (Box 611)
      - Correspondence, 1963-1969 (Box 611)
      - Publicity, 1966 (Box 612)
      - Royalties, Margaret Ramsay (E-408), 1963-1970 (Box 612)
  - Ruitenbeek, Hendrik M.
    - Correspondence, author, 1961; 1964-1967,; 1973-1975 (Box 612)
    - Heirs to Freud
      - Contract, 1965 (Box 612)
      - Correspondence, 1965-1970 (Box 612)
      - Production, Jacket (Box 612)
      - Production, Typescript (rough), some is just clippings or photocopies pasted onto sheets of paper; 2 folders (Box 612)
      - Publicity, Grove, 1966-1967 (Box 612)
      - Publicity, General, 1966-1967 (Box 612)
      - Royalties (E-418), 1967-1971 (Box 612)
      - Royalties (GP-362), 1964-1970 (Box 612)
      - Royalties, Evergreen Book Club (GP-362), 1968-1969 (Box 612)
    - Freud, the Women in His Life
      - Project file, 1974-1975; undated; sales pitch, correspondence, table of contents, partial typescript (Box 612)
      - Publicity, Grove (Box 612)
  - Rulfo, Juan
    - Correspondence, author, 1958-1959; 1964,; 1969; in Spanish; includes some with Lysander Kemp (Box 612)
    - Correspondence about, 1981 (Box 612)
    - Llano en Llamas [The Burning Plain]
      - Correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 612)
    - Pedro Paramo
      - Correspondence, 1958-1972 (Box 612)
      - Production, Camera copy (Box 612)
      - Production, Corrections, miscellaneous (Box 612)
      - Production, Jacket, includes drafts of blurb (Box 612)
      - Production, Shot copy, disbound Evergreen edition (Box 612)
      - Publicity, Grove, 1957-1964 (Box 613)
      - Publicity, General, 1959-1960; 1965-1966 (Box 613)
      - Royalties (E-149), 1958-1961 (Box 613)
      - Royalties, Fondo de Culturas (B-207), 1969-1970 (Box 613)
  - Rumaker, Michael
    - Correspondence, Author, 1964-1968; 1971,; 1973,; 1977 (Box 613)
    - Gringos and Other Stories
      - Contracts, 1966; 1973-1974,; undated; includes Evergreen Book Club contract; copyright forms (Box 613)
      - Correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box 613)
      - Production, Jacket (Box 613)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1968 (Box 613)
      - Production, Mechanicals, pp. 1-170; 3 folders (Box 613)
      - Production, Mechanicals, pp. 171-214, back matter (Box 614)
      - Production, Shot copy, disbound Penguin edition (Box 614)
      - Publicity, Grove, 1967-1968 (Box 614)
      - Publicity, General, 1966-1968; 2 folders (Box 614)
      - Rights and permissions, 1967; 1972; includes permission to quote a letter from Rossett to Rumaker (Box 614)
      - Royalties, Evergreen Book Club (GP-408), 1968-1969 (Box 614)
      - Royalties, Harold Ober Associates (B-168), 1968-1970 (Box 614)
      - Royalties, Harold Ober Associates (GP-408), 1966-1970 (Box 614)
      - Royalties, Scribner's (GP-408), 1969-1970; 1973 (Box 614)
    - [untitled novel]
      - Royalties, Harold Ober Associates, 1966-1970 (Box 614)
  - Russian Revolutionary Posters
    - Correspondence, 1966-1968; 1972; mostly correspondence with Gerhardt Verlag; includes Grove publicity brochure with small black-and-white photos of posters (Box 614)
    - Publicity, 1967 (Box 614)
  - Russoli
    - The History of Art, art book, with Arnoldo Mondadori
      - Project file, 1962; correpondence, 189-page typescript carbon in Italian (Box 614)
  - Sachs, Wulf
    - Black Anger, possible alternate title: Black Hamlet
      - Contracts, 1968-1969; 1976; includes a few items of correspondence with Little, Brown & Co. (Box 614)
      - Correspondence, 1956-1957; 1961,; 1969; most is with Little, Brown & Co. (Box 614)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1968-1969 (Box 614)
      - Publicity, 1969 (Box 614)
      - Royalties, Little, Brown & Co. (B-206), 1969-1970 (Box 614)
      - Royalties, Little, Brown & Co. (E-60), 1956-1964; includes copy of license agreement (Box 614)
  - de Sade, Marquis
    is also the repository for the
    papers of Austryn Wainhouse
    , who translated all of Sade for Grove Press and worked closely with Dick Seaver on the books. More on Grove's translation and publication of Sade's works may be found in that collection.
    - Bibliography, galleys from unidentified book (Box 615)
    - Chicago trial, 1967 (Box 615)
    - Correspondence, general, 1952-1953; 1965,; 1969 (Box 615)
    - Pennsylvania v. Ruttenberg, Katz and Ruttenberg, 1970 (Box 615)
    - 120 Days of Sodom
      - Contract, Austryn Wainhouse (translator), 1965 (Box 615)
      - Correspondence, Austryn Wainhouse (translator), 1964-1967 (Box 615)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1976; 1978,; 1980 (Box 615)
      - Project file, 1965-1967; 1970; correspondence, check requests, notes (Box 615)
      - Publicity, Grove (Box 615)
      - Publicity, General, 1966-1967 (Box 615)
      - Royalties, Evergreen Book Club (GP-371), 1967-1970 (Box 615)
      - Royalties, Hudson Book Club (GP-371), 1966-1968 (Box 615)
      - Royalties, Mid-Century Book Society (GP-371), 1966 (Box 615)
      - Royalties, Readers' Subscription (GP-371), 1967-1969 (Box 615)
      - Royalties, Seaver and Wainhouse (B-138), 1967-1970 (Box 615)
      - Royalties, Seaver and Wainhouse (GP-371), 1965-1970 (Box 615)
    - Journal Inedit
      - Project file, 1968; 1970-1971 (Box 615)
    - Juliette
      See also Anonymous: The Pleasures of Cruelty: Being a Sequel to the Reading of Justine et Juliette by the Marquis de Sade.
      - Correspondence, Austryn Wainhouse (translator), 1966-1969; 2 folders (Box 615)
      - Correspondence, Jeanne Duell (copy editor), 1967-1968 (Box 615)
      - Drawings, circa 1968; reproductions, unidentified source (Box 615)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1976; 1978 (Box 615)
      - Production, Manuscript / setting copy, front matter, foreword, Part 1, Part 2, Part 3 (incomplete), Part 4 (incomplete), Part 5, Part 6; 11 folders (Box 616)
      - Production, Setting copy, Parts 1 through 6 (partial); 9 folders (Box 617)
      - Production, Setting copy, rest of Part 6; 2 folders (Box 618)
      - Project file, 1966-1968; 1978; correspondence, jacket, jacket copy, package log, production estimates, copies of Seaver and Wainhouse contracts, miscellaneous notes (Box 618)
      - Publicity, Grove (Box 618)
      - Publicity, General, 1968-1969 (Box 618)
      - Royalties, Wainhouse (B-178), 1968-1971 (Box 618)
      - Royalties, Wainhouse (B-178), 1969-1970 (Box 618)
      - Royalties, Evergreen Book Club (GP-444), 1968-1969 (Box 618)
      - Royalties, Wainhouse (GP-444), 1966-1970 (Box 618)
      - Style sheets and corrections, 1967 (Box 618)
    - Justine, or, the Misfortunes of Virtue, comic book version, illustrated and adapted by Zepol
      - Contract, Agence Dalmas, 1968 (Box 618)
      - Drawings, 1968; glossy photo-reproductions of illustrations from the French original (Box 618)
      - French text (Box 618)
      - Photos, Zepol, 1968 (Box 618)
      - Production, manufacturing, 1968-1970 (Box 618)
      - Project file, 1968-1970; correspondence with Agence Dalmas, production estimates, notes (Box 618)
      - Royalties, Richard Seaver (translator), 1966-1971 (Box 618)
    - Justine, Philosophy in the Bedroom and other writings
      - Contracts, Seaver and Wainhouse (editor and translator), 1966 (Box 619)
      - Correspondence, Wainhouse (translator), 1963-1965 (Box 619)
      - Photographs, 1964-1965; includes black-and-white photographs and photoreproductions of drawings, a few strips of negatives (Box 619)
      - Production, Camera copy, front matter through p. 699; 5 folders (Box 619)
      - Production, Camera copy, pp. 700-752, miscellaneous pages; 2 folders (Box 620)
      - Production, Illustrations, positive and negative prints of drawings, sketches for layout; includes one for Plexus by Henry Miller (Box 620)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1977-1979 (Box 620)
      - Production, Manuscript, front matter and foreword (Box 620)
      - Production, Proof copy (F&Gs), incomplete; pp. 75-743; 3 folders (Box 620)
      - Project file, 1959; 1963-1970; correspondence, including letters to various important writers (e.g. Sontag, Burroughs Rechy, etc.) inviting them to read and review the book (Box 620)
      - Project file, photocopies of foreword and preface manuscript, copy of contract, catalog from a French publisher, notes, etc. (Box 620)
      - Publicity, Grove, includes correspondence with reviewers and booksellers, press releases, brochures, newspapers advertisements, etc.; 3 folders (Box 621)
      - Publicity, General, 1965-1966; 2 folders (Box 621)
      - Rights and permissions, 1968 (Box 621)
      - Royalties, Caedmon Records (GP-346), 1966-1969 (Box 621)
      - Royalties, Evergreen Book Club (GP-346), 1966-1970 (Box 621)
      - Royalties, Gummerus (GP-346), 1969 (Box 621)
      - Royalties, Hudson Book Club (HB-346), 1965-1968 (Box 621)
      - Royalties, Mid-Century Book Society (GP-346), 1965-1967 (Box 621)
      - Royalties, Parallax (B-148), 1968-1969 (Box 621)
      - Royalties, Parallax (B-5407), 1966-1970; Black Cat (Box 621)
      - Royalties, Parallax (GP-346), 1969-1970 (Box 621)
      - Royalties, Readers' Subscription (GP-346), 1965-1969 (Box 621)
      - Royalties, Seaver and Wainhouse (B-148), 1968-1969 (Box 621)
      - Royalties, Seaver and Wainhouse (B-5407), 1966-1970 (Box 621)
      - Royalties, Seaver and Wainhouse (GP-346), 1963-1970 (Box 621)
    - Le Voyage d'Italie
      - Correspondence, 1968 (Box 621)
    - Letters from the Bastille and Vincennes
      - Correspondence, Wainhouse (translator), 1967-1970 (Box 622)
      - Project file, 1967-1968; contracts with Wainhouse and Pauvert, glossy photos and negatives of illustrations, notes, etc. (Box 622)
    - The Mystified Magistrate and other stories
      - Project file, 1970; includes Black Cat edition jacket (Box 622)
    - Sixty Erotic Engravings from Juliette
      - Project file, 1969-1970; correspondence, including a letter from Dick Seaver outlining the history of the illustrated edition, mention of The Amorous Illustrations of Thomas Rowlandson, notes, etc. (Box 622)
      - Royalties, Sevaer (GP-607), 1969-1970 (Box 622)
      - Royalties, Evergreen Book Club (GP-607), 1969-1970 (Box 622)
  - Sadie, Stanley
    - Handel
      - Project file, 1959-1960; correspondence, selected discography and bibliography (Box 622)
      - Typescript, revised (Box 622)
  - Sadinet, Jean
    - Les Plaisirs du Roi
      - Contracts, 1968 (Box 622)
      - Royalties, Agence Hoffman / Terrain Vague, 1968-1971 (Box 622)
  - Sadler, Mark
    - The Falling Man
      - Contracts, 1972 (Box 622)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1970-1971 (Box 622)
  - Sadut, Claude
    - Les Jeux de l'Orgueil [The Pride Games]
      - Contracts, 1969-1970 (Box 622)
      - Correspondence, reader's report, 1969 (Box 622)
      - Royalties, Borchardt / Pauvert, 1969-1971 (Box 622)
  - Sager, Clifford et al., with Thomas Brayboy and Barbara Waxenberg
    - Black Ghetto Family in Therapy
      - Contracts, 1969; includes proposal to publish (Box 622)
      - Correspondence, author and others, 1969-1970; majority is with Clifford Sager but also includes correspondence with Brayboy and Waxenberg, person who appeared in the cover photo, reader's reports, etc. (Box 622)
      - Production, Jacket, includes various drafts of jacket copy (Box 622)
      - Production, Setting copy, 2 folders (Box 622)
      - Production, Miscellaneous, typed and handwritten corrections from Waxenberg and others, typed and revised rough of title page for GP-619 (Box 622)
      - Publicity, Grove, 1970; includes author photographs (with negatives) and publicity questionnaires (Box 622)
      - Publicity, General, 1970 (Box 623)
      - Royalties, Sager (GP-619), 1969-1970 (Box 623)
      - Writings by Sager, 1967-1969; reprints of articles: An overview of family therapy (1968), Diagnosis and treatment of marital conflicts (1967), Transference in conjoint treatment of married couples (1967), Selection and engagement of patients in family therapy (1968), program for 1969 annual conference with description of Sager's panel (Box 623)
  - St. George, Andrew
    - [untitled book on Haiti affair]
      - Project file, 1970; 1972; correspondence, clipping, book outline (Box 623)
  - St. George, George
    - Correspondence, author, 1964-1965; 1969; relating to proposed books on UFOs, sexual segregation (Box 623)
  - St. Laurent, Yves
    - La Vilaine Lulu
      - Project file, 1967; correspondence, clipping from French press (Box 623)
  - Salama, Hannu
    - Midsummer Dance
      - Project file, 1964-1965; correspondence with Anselm Hollo and others, clippings from Finnish and English press regarding blasphemy trial, English translations of problem section (Box 623)
  - Salas, Floyd
    - Correspondence, author, 1967-1971; includes photographs of Salas (Box 623)
    - Correspondence, general, 1968-1971 (Box 623)
    - Gin for Xmas
      - Contracts, 1968; includes proposal to publish (Box 623)
      - Correspondence, 1967-1971; includes 35-page typescript identified in a letter as "the first three chapters of his second draft" (Box 623)
    - Tattoo the Wicked Cross
      - Contracts, 1966-1970; includes proposal to publish (Box 623)
      - Correspondence, 1966-1970; includes reader's report, correspondence with Victor Urban of Arkansas Penitentiary regarding cover photo of Charles Edward Gardner, release for motion picture rights (Box 623)
      - Production, Jacket, hardcover and paperback editions, includes boards for hardcover (Box 623)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1968; hardcover and paperback editions; 2 folders (Box 623)
      - Production, Marked copy, for Black Cat paperback edition; 2 folders (Box 624)
      - Production, Setting copy, 2 folders (Box 624)
      - Production, Miscellaneous, bills, paperwork, 30 pages of photocopied typescript (Box 624)
      - Publicity, Grove, 1967-1968; correspondnece, press releases, letter from John Rechy, newspaper ads, photographs of book and of author; 3 folders (Box 624)
      - Publicity, General, 1967-1968; includes long article on the 67th American Bookseller's Association conference (because it has a photo of Grove's booth with the Salas book); 2 folders (Box 625)
      - Royalties, Borchardt (GP-403), 1968-1969 (Box 625)
      - Royalties, Evergreen Book Club (GP-403), 1967-1969 (Box 625)
      - Royalties, Horch / Caralt (GP-403), 1968-1971 (Box 625)
      - Royalties, Robert Lescher (B-156), 1968-1971 (Box 625)
      - Royalties, Robert Lescher (GP-403), 1966-1971; includes some correspondence (Box 625)
    - What Now, My Love?
      - Correspondence, 1968-1971 (Box 625)
      - Production, Jacket, hardcover and paperback (Box 625)
      - Production, Manufacturing, hardcover and paperback editions; 2 folders (Box 625)
      - Production, Marked copy, disbound Grove hardcover edition (Box 625)
      - Production, Setting copy (Box 625)
      - Production, Typescript, "revised 11/68" (Box 625)
      - Publicity, Grove, 1970 (Box 625)
      - Royalties, Graphic Productions (GP-568), 1970 (Box 626)
      - Royalties, Hayakawa Shobo Ltd. (GP-568) [empty folder] (Box 626)
      - Royalties, Robert Lescher (B-305), 1971 (Box 626)
      - Royalties, Robert Lescher (GP-568), 1968-1971 (Box 626)
  - Sameth, Sigmund
    - Nine Whores
      - Project file, 1972; author correspondence, cover sketch, 5pp of typescript (Box 626)
  - Sandbach, Gordon K.
    - Which Way to Java
      - Project file, author correspondence describing book as "Jonathan Livingston Seagull, applied," photocopied clipping about Tarzan (Box 626)
  - Sanchez Salazar, Gustav A., See Gonzalez, Luis J.: The Great Rebel - with Gustavo A. Sanchez Salazar
  - Sanders, Ed
    - Correspondence, author, 1969-1970; undated (Box 626)
    - Duck Butter
      - Contracts, 1967-1968 (Box 626)
      - Correspondence, 1967-1972 (Box 626)
      - Royalties, Edmiston, 1968-1971 (Box 626)
    - The Hairy Table
      - Project file, "an autobiographical novel (with historical flashbacks relevant to the story"; clipping of article by Sanders, letter to Sanders, chapter outline (Box 626)
    - Shards of God
      - Contracts, Fainting Phantom Press, 1969 (Box 626)
      - Correspondence, 1969-1972; undated; also includes lengthy lists of names mentioned in the manuscript, proofreader's style sheet, design sheet, reader's report, notes, etc. (Box 626)
      - Production, Manuscript, "early draft, do not use for setting" (Box 626)
      - Production, Marked copy, disbound Grove hardcover edition (Box 626)
      - Production, Plate proofs (Box 626)
      - Production, Setting copy (Box 626)
      - Publicity, 1970 (Box 626)
      - Releases, 1969-1970; releases from individuals mentioned in the book, incluiding Allen Ginsburg, Bob Fass, Abby Hoffman, Gerard Malanga, Paul Krasner, Jerry Rubin, more (Box 626)
      - Royalties, Sanders (B-302), 1971-1972 (Box 626)
      - Royalties, Sanders (GP-360), 1969-1970 (Box 626)
  - Sanderson, Stewart
    - Ernest Hemingway
      - Correspondence, 1958-1962 (Box 626)
      - Permissions, 1959-1961; for use of quotations from various Hemingway novels (Box 626)
      - Production, Jacket, Grove edition, also jacket from the Oliver & Boyd edition (Box 626)
      - Production, Manufacturing, 1961; undated; typed sheets for title, half-title, copyright page; billing; letter to Oliver & Boyd about covers (Box 626)
      - Production, Proof copy (F&Gs) (Box 627)
      - Production, Quotations, 1959; folder labeled "translation and references" containing quotations from Hemingway and other authors, on typed fragments taped or pasted together (Box 627)
      - Production, Shot copy, 1961 (Box 627)
      - Royalties, Oliver & Boyd (EP-7), 1961-1968 (Box 627)
  - Sankawulo, Wilton G. Sengbe
    - The Story of a Native African
      - Project file, 1966-1967; author correspondence, reader's reports (Box 627)
  - Santa, Ferenc
    - Husz Hora: Vingt Heures [Twenty Hours]
      - Project file, reader's report, in French (Box 627)
  - Santini, Rosemary
    - The Secret Fire
      - Offsetting copy, disbound unidentified edition (Box 627)
  - Sarraute, Nathalie
    - Photograph, author (Box 627)
  - Sarrazin, Albertine
    - L'Astragale
      - Contracts, 1965-1968; joint contract with The Runaway; also contains copyright forms (Box 627)
      - Correspondence, 1965-1970; translator Patsy Southgate, others (Box 627)
      - Production, Jacket, includes drafts of jacket copy, permissions for use of movie still for cover (Box 627)
      - Production, Manufacturing (Box 627)
      - Production, Miscellaneous, few pages of revised typescript; typed roughs for title, half-title, copyright; handwritten lists of corrections (Box 627)
      - Production, Setting copy, typescript with corrections (Box 627)
      - Production, Shot copy (Box 628)
      - Publicity, General, 1968; undated; includes clippings of advertisement in French press (Box 628)
      - Rights and permissions, 1967-1968 (Box 628)
      - Royalties, Borchardt (B-221), 1971 (Box 628)
      - Royalties, Borchardt (GP-373), 1965-1970 (Box 628)
      - Royalties, Evergreen Book Club (GP-395), 1968-1969 (Box 628)
    - Cold Country [La Traversiere]
      - Project file, 1966-1971; correspondence, reader's reports, clippings, royalty forms, contracts, etc. (Box 628)
    - The Runaway
      - Contracts, 1965; 1968; includes copyright forms (Box 628)
      - Correspondence, 1965-1968; translator Charles Lam Markmann, Pauvert, others; includes list of corrections from author, 5/26/1967 (Box 628)
      - Production, Jacket (Box 628)
      - Production, Setting copy, heavily revised, including a complete change from past tense to present tense; 3 folders (Box 628)
      - Production, Shot copy, includes boards; 3 folders (Box 628)
      - Production, Miscellaneous, manufacturing costs, several pages of corrections (in French) (Box 629)
      - Publicity, undated; includes several items in French (Box 629)
      - Royalties, Borchardt (B-224) [empty folder] (Box 629)
      - Royalties, Borchardt (GP-395), 1965-1971 (Box 629)
  - Sartre, Jean-Paul
    - Anti-Semite and Jew
      - Contracts, 1960; 1962,; 1964 (Box 629)
      - Correspondence, 1958-1966; includes discussion of Sartre's works in general, proposal to publish, copy of lawsuit from creditors against Sartre and Les Editions Nagel (Box 629)
      - Publicity, 1962-1965 (Box 629)
      - Royalties, Schocken (BA-15), 1962-1965 (Box 629)
      - Royalties, Schocken (E-273), 1960-1966 (Box 629)
  - Saunders, Marion
    - The House with the Curtains Drawn
      - Correspondence, Gordon Grimley, 1972; includes contract, check requests (Box 629)
  - Sauneron, Serge
    - The Priests of Ancient Egypt
      - Project file, 1958-1962; 1965,; 1980; jacket, correspondence about photographs, notes from translator Ann Morrisett about difficult words, etc. (Box 629)
      - Production, Working copy, Evergreen Profile edition with correction/change slips (Box 629)
      - Publicity, 1961 (Box 629)
      - Royalties, Borchardt (P-12), 1962-1965 (Box 629)
  - Schechner, Donald
    - Makbeth
      - Contracts, 1970; includes some correspondence (Box 629)
      - Royalties, Robert Lantz / Candida Donadio, 1970-1971 (Box 629)
  - Scheer, Robert, See Zeitlin, Maurice: Cuba: Tragedy in our Hemisphere.
  - Scheffler, Linda
    - Help Thy Neighbor
      - Production, Manufacturing (Box 629)
      - Production, Proofreader's copies, printouts of computer files, which do not map exactly to chapters; multiple copies of each printout with different revisions, printer codes, etc.; 10 folders (Box 629)